couponsdealsandmore.com 2018-12-10

# Privacy Policy

GDPR wants plain speak on this, so here is my “plain speak”:

Summation: assume your IP is being tracked online. Always. If you sign up for a newsletter, you are giving people access to your email address and IP address. Why? This “free” content (social media, blogs, news sites, sports sites, etc) is not actually free. It costs money to run a website. Sooooo since the content is “free to you” (generic you) ads pay the bills. Remember: if you are not paying for the product, you are the product.

Now, with that in mind, here is more information on [ Ann’s Entitled Life ](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/) data collection.

## AnnsEntitledLife.com Privacy Policy

The privacy of our visitors to [ Ann’s Entitled Life ](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/) is important to us.

At [ Ann’s Entitled Life, ](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/) we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit [ Ann’s Entitled Life, ](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/) and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

• Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL, Verizon, Spectrum, etc), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Chrome or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

• Cookies and Web Beacons

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

• Automatically-Collected Information

We automatically collect certain information about you and the device with which you access [AnnsEntitledLife.com.](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/) For example, when you use [ Ann’s Entitled Life ](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/) we will log your IP address, operating system type, browser type, referring website, pages you viewed, and the dates/times when you accessed [ Ann’s Entitled Life. ](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/) We may also collect information about actions you take when using [ Ann’s Entitled Life ](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/) such as links clicked.

We also use third party advertisements on [ Ann’s Entitled Life ](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/) to support this website. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

• Information We Collect from Others

We may receive information about you from other sources. You may link your website account in your comments or user profile on [ Ann’s Entitled Life. ](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/) If you choose to leave a comment or link your website account in your user profile or comments, we will receive your name, email address and profile picture associated with that account.

 **How Your Information May Be Used**

We may use the information collected in the following ways:

• To operate and maintain [AnnsEntitledLife.com](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/)  
• To send you promotional information, such as newsletters. Each email promotion will provide information on how to opt-out of future mailings.  
• To send you administrative communications, such as administrative emails, confirmation emails, technical notices, updates on policies, or security alerts.  
• To respond to your comments or inquiries.  
• To provide you with user support.  
• To track and measure advertising on [ Ann’s Entitled Life.](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/)  
• To protect, investigate, and deter against any unauthorized or illegal activity.

 **Third-party Use of Personal Data**

We may share your information with third parties when you explicitly authorize us to share your information. Additionally, [AnnsEntitledLife.com](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/) may use third-party service providers to service various aspects of [AnnsEntitledLife.com.](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/) Each third-party service provider’s use of your personal information is dictated by their respective privacy policies.

[AnnsEntitledLife.com](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/) currently uses the following third-party service providers:

Google Analytics – this service tracks Website usage and provides information such as referring websites and user actions on [AnnsEntitledLife.com.](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/) Google Analytics may capture your IP address. Read google’s privacy policy for more details.

MailChimp – this service is used for delivery of email updates and newsletters. We store your name and email address for purposes of delivering such communications. Please read MailChimp’s privacy policy for more information.

Sumome – this service is used to send you push notifications through your web browser, should you choose. Please read Sumome’s privacy policy for more information.

Currently, your personal information is not shared with any other third-party applications. This may be amended solely at this website’s [(AnnsEntitledLife.com)](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/) discretion.

Except when required by law, we will not sell, distribute, or reveal your email addresses or other personal information without your consent; however, we may disclose or transfer personal information collected through [AnnsEntitledLife.com](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/) to third parties who acquire all or a portion of our business, which may be the result of a merger, consolidation, or purchase of all or a portion of our assets, or in connection with any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding brought by or against us.

• Publicly Visible Information

If you create a user profile on [AnnsEntitledLife.com](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/) or leave a comment, certain information may be publicly visible. To create a user profile, you must choose a username and password and input your email address for profile confirmation. Your email address will never be available publicly. Users may see your username, profile description, and website information.

 **Advertising**

• Display Ads

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve content and advertisements when you visit [AnnsEntitledLife.com](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/) which may use cookies, as discussed above.

• Retargeting Ads

Ocassionally [AnnsEntitledLife.com](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/) may engage in remarketing efforts with third-party companies, such as Google, Facebook, Pinterest, or Instagram, in order to market [AnnsEntitledLife.com.](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/) These companies use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to [AnnsEntitledLife.com.](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/)

• Affiliate Program Participation

[AnnsEntitledLife.com](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/) may engage in affiliate marketing, which is done by embedding tracking links into [AnnsEntitledLife.com.](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/) If you click on a link from an affiliate partnership, a cookie will be placed on your browser to track any sales for purposes of commissions.

We are a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for us to earn fees by linking to Amazon.com and affiliated sites.

• Newsletters

On [AnnsEntitledLife.com](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/) you may [subscribe to our newsletter,](http://eepurl.com/Ak67H) via MailChimp which may be used for advertising purposes. All newsletters sent may contain tracking pixels. The pixel is embedded in emails and allows an analysis of the success of online marketing campaigns. Because of these tracking pixels, we may see if and when you open an email and which links within the email you click. This also allows [AnnsEntitledLife.com](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/) to adapt the content of future newsletters to the interests of the user. This behavior will not be passed on to third parties.

Please note that we may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes or to complete transactions, or when required by law.

• Sensitive Information

At no time should you submit sensitive personal information to [AnnsEntitledLife.com.](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/) This includes your social security number, information regarding race or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious beliefs, health information, criminal background, home address, telephone numbers, or any type of credit card information. If you do submit such information to us, it will be subject to this Privacy Policy.

• Children’s Information:

[AnnsEntitledLife.com](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/) does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 16.

I can always be reached for Privacy Policy questions through my [ contact me page](https://www.annsentitledlife.com/contactus/) or by [emailing me directly!](mailto:annsentitledlife@yahoo.com.com)

* * *

FOLLOW US ON:
